Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Maid=
=الخادمة=
=Episode 22=
=الحلقة 22=
It was you?
هل كنت أنت؟
Prepare the horses.
جهزوا الخيول.
Head to the palace.
توجه إلى القصر.
Understood.
مفهومة.
By the Empress Dowager's decree,
بموجب مرسوم الإمبراطورة الأرملة،
Her Grace is unwell today.
سموها مريضة اليوم.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
please return.
يرجى العودة.
I will remain here
سأبقى هنا
and kneel until Her Grace recovers.
وركع حتى تتعافى جلالتها.
Your Grace,
صاحب السمو،
Ye Xiyan
يي شيان
actually knelt outside all night.
في الواقع ركعت خارجًا طوال الليل.
The Prince Regent
الأمير الوصي
accompanied her through the night.
رافقها طوال الليل.
Good.
جيد.
She is indeed a useful pawn.
إنها في الواقع بيدق مفيد.
Summon her.
استدعيها.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Consort Ye, don't worry.
يا رفيقة، لا تقلقي.
Zhao is being cared for
تشاو يتم الاعتناء به
by my personal nanny.
من قبل مربيتي الشخصية.
Your Grace,
صاحب السمو،
Zhao is my own flesh and blood.
تشاو هو لحمي ودمي.
As long as you spare him,
ما دام أنك توفره،
I'll do anything you command.
سأفعل أي شيء تأمرني به.
You're clever enough
أنت ذكي بما فيه الكفاية
to understand
لفهم
what I truly desire.
ما أرغب فيه حقا.
Pei Ji...
باي جي...
Take his life.
خذ حياته.
I'll let you leave with the child.
سأدعك تغادر مع الطفل.
Shen Yuanjin
شين يوانجين
will also be yours to handle.
وسوف تكون لك أيضًا للتعامل معها.
I await your success.
أنتظر نجاحك.
I
أنا
will fulfill the task.
سوف يقوم بالمهمة.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
The Empress Dowager claims
تدعي الإمبراطورة الأرملة
only surrendering your military authority
فقط تسليم سلطتك العسكرية
can ensure Zhao's safety.
يمكن ضمان سلامة تشاو.
Today,
اليوم،
I'll give you the tiger tally.
سأعطيك حصيلة النمر.
All my actions
كل أفعالي
are to protect those I cherish.
لحماية من أعزهم.
(Pei Ji,)
(باي جي،)
(turns out I never truly knew you.)
(اتضح أنني لم أعرفك حقًا أبدًا.)
Your Grace,
صاحب السمو،
Xiyan is an outsider, after all.
شييان هو شخص غريب، بعد كل شيء.
I'm your blood relative.
أنا قريبك من الدم.
How could you trust her?
كيف يمكنك أن تثق بها؟
I care only for results.
أنا أهتم فقط بالنتائج.
Kill Pei Ji,
اقتل باي جي،
and you'll be mother to the Prince Paramount.
وستكونين أمًا للأمير باراماونت.
You're my true niece by blood.
أنت ابنة أخي الحقيقية بالدم.
Naturally, I wish to support you most.
بطبيعة الحال، أتمنى أن أدعمك أكثر.
Since you're determined,
بما أنك مصمم،
I'll share this with you.
سأشارك هذا معك.
The four generals of the Western Army intend to defect.
أربعة جنرالات من الجيش الغربي ينوي الانشقاق
I've promised them
لقد وعدتهم
that after our victory,
أنه بعد انتصارنا،
they'll be ennobled as non-imperial princes.
سيتم ترقيتهم إلى مرتبة الأمراء غير الإمبراطوريين.
So you've already...
إذًا لديك بالفعل...
But confronting Pei Ji directly
لكن مواجهة باي جي مباشرة
makes them hesitant.
يجعلهم مترددين.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
one of them still resents
واحد منهم لا يزال مستاء
your father's past mistreatment
سوء معاملة والدك في الماضي
of his family.
من عائلته.
Your Grace,
صاحب السمو،
what do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
♪Wind comes but never stays by her side♪
♪تأتي الريح ولكنها لا تبقى بجانبها أبدًا♪
Isn't my mother supposed
أليس من المفترض أن أمي
to stay with my aunt these days?
أن أبقى مع خالتي هذه الأيام؟
Why return so abruptly?
لماذا العودة فجأة؟
It makes me miss
إنه يجعلني أفتقد
the Lantern Fair.
معرض الفوانيس.
My lady, slow down.
سيدتي، أبطئي.
♪A fleeting light warmed the dark♪
♪ضوء عابر يدفئ الظلام♪
♪Amid the crowd, you're my only care♪
♪وسط الحشد، أنت اهتمامي الوحيد♪
♪- I spin round after round - I orbit back around♪
♪- أدور حول دائرة بعد دائرة - أدور حولها مرة أخرى♪
♪Too scared to stay♪
♪خائف جدًا من البقاء♪
My lady, you...
سيدتي، أنت...
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
My lady, I...
سيدتي، أنا...
The lady awaits.
السيدة تنتظر.
You're a maid?
هل أنت خادمة؟
I'm the new guard,
أنا الحارس الجديد
Changyi.
تشانغي.
♪- Unmoved by the sorrow - I still linger♪
♪- لا أتأثر بالحزن - ما زلت أتردد♪
♪Love and hate entangle, not only in the past♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، ليس فقط في الماضي♪
♪The past blinds me, gone in a moment♪
♪الماضي يعميني، ذهب في لحظة♪
♪Stars fall again beyond the hill♪
♪النجوم تسقط مرة أخرى خلف التل♪
♪- Moon-bright heart, dust never clings - Bound with you♪
♪- قلب مشرق كالقمر، الغبار لا يلتصق أبدًا - مرتبط بك♪
I
أنا
made this myself.
لقد صنعت هذا بنفسي.
♪Wind comes but never stays by her side♪
♪تأتي الريح ولكنها لا تبقى بجانبها أبدًا♪
♪Through the crowd, a searing glance♪
♪من خلال الحشد، نظرة حارقة♪
♪- I spin round after round - I orbit back around♪
♪- أدور حول دائرة بعد دائرة - أدور حولها مرة أخرى♪
♪Too scared to stay♪
♪خائف جدًا من البقاء♪
Why give it to me?
لماذا تعطيه لي؟
I...
أنا...
I admire you.
أنا معجب بك.
I want to marry you.
أريد الزواج منك.
If you agree,
إذا وافقت،
I'll beg Madam for your freedom.
سأتوسل إلى سيدتي من أجل حريتك.
My monthly wages will all be yours.
أجوري الشهرية كلها ستكون لك.
My family still has
عائلتي لا تزال لديها
some fertile land back home.
بعض الأراضي الخصبة في الوطن.
I...
أنا...
♪Stars fall again beyond the hill♪
♪النجوم تسقط مرة أخرى خلف التل♪
♪- Moon-bright heart, dust never clings - Bound with you♪
♪- قلب مشرق كالقمر، الغبار لا يلتصق أبدًا - مرتبط بك♪
♪Moon-bright heart, dust never clings♪
♪قلب مشرق كالقمر، الغبار لا يلتصق أبدًا♪
♪This dream, serene delight♪
♪هذا الحلم، متعة هادئة♪
You fool!
يا أحمق!
You're about to wed the Prince Regent,
أنت على وشك الزواج من الأمير الوصي،
yet fall in love with this trash?
ولكن هل تقع في حب هذه القمامة؟
My lady,
سيدتي،
it's all my fault.
إنه خطئي كله.
Yuanjin is innocent.
يوانجين بريء.
My lady.
سيدتي.
Guards.
حراس.
Castrate him.
خصيه.
No. My lady!
لا سيدتي!
- Changyi. - My lady.
- تشانغي. - سيدتي.
- Mother. - My lady!
- أمي. - سيدتي!
I was the one who got him drunk and seduced him.
أنا من جعله يسكر وأغويه.
It wasn't his fault.
لم يكن خطؤه.
I have my own feelings too.
لدي مشاعري الخاصة أيضاً.
I don't want to be your pawn in a political marriage.
لا أريد أن أكون بيدقك في زواج سياسي.
Every action demands a price.
لكل فعل ثمن.
Can you abandon the glory of the Duke's Mansion,
هل يمكنك التخلي عن مجد قصر الدوق،
and renounce your title as Princess Consort
وتتنازل عن لقبك كأميرة قرينة
to become a mere guard's wife?
لتصبح مجرد زوجة حارس؟
Jin,
إحساس،
I'll take you away.
سوف آخذك بعيدا.
To somewhere nobody knows us.
إلى مكان لا يعرفنا فيه أحد.
Though I can't offer you current luxuries,
على الرغم من أنني لا أستطيع أن أقدم لك الرفاهيات الحالية،
I'll never let you
لن اسمح لك ابدا
suffer even a little.
عاني حتى لو قليلا.
That's just fine.
هذا جيد تماما.
This way,
من هنا،
you can accompany me
يمكنك مرافقتي
to the Prince Regent's Mansion after my marriage.
إلى قصر الأمير ريجنت بعد زواجي.
We'll stay together forever.
سوف نبقى معا إلى الأبد.
Jin.
إحساس.
Is this truly what you desire?
هل هذا حقا ما ترغب فيه؟
When Zhao becomes Prince Paramount
عندما أصبح تشاو الأمير باراماونت
and obtains the ironclad edict,
ويحصل على المرسوم الحديدي،
we'll take him to Jiangnan.
سنأخذه إلى جيانجنان.
In that land of literary elegance
في تلك الأرض ذات الأناقة الأدبية
and gentle prosperity, we'll live in honored peace,
والازدهار اللطيف، سنعيش في سلام مشرف،
never returning to the capital.
عدم العودة إلى العاصمة أبدًا.
(The wealth and glory are mirages.)
(إن الثروة والمجد سراب)
(Those within move like soulless husks,)
(أولئك الذين في الداخل يتحركون مثل قشور بلا روح)
(resembling demons and monsters.)
(يشبه الشياطين والوحوش.)
(None remains human.)
(لم يبق إنسان.)
(All devour each other.)
(الجميع يلتهمون بعضهم البعض.)
(Why can't you let go?)
(لماذا لا تستطيع أن تترك؟)
♪I once fell into deep love♪
♪لقد وقعت في حب عميق ذات مرة♪
♪Caught in a drama of love and hate♪
♪وقعت في دراما الحب والكراهية♪
♪Trapped in self-made cages♪
♪محاصرون في أقفاص من صنعهم♪
♪To whom should I direct my questions♪
♪إلى من أوجه أسئلتي♪
♪Heal my wounds from past dreams♪
♪ شفاء جروحي من أحلام الماضي ♪
♪Fate bestowed me both joy and pain♪
♪لقد منحني القدر كل من الفرح والألم♪
♪Left me a kiss of love and hate♪
♪ترك لي قبلة من الحب والكراهية♪
♪Who will unravel my dreams so deep♪
♪من سيكشف أحلامي العميقة؟♪
♪Who will save me from this lonely place♪
♪من سينقذني من هذا المكان الوحيد♪
♪Who will give me back my lonely grace♪
♪من سيعيد لي نعمتي الوحيدة♪
♪I dare not ask the infatuated ones♪
♪لا أجرؤ على سؤال المغرمين♪
♪As the moonlight thickens♪
♪مع ازدياد كثافة ضوء القمر♪
♪What I await♪
♪ما أنتظره♪
♪Which heartless soul♪
♪أي روح بلا قلب♪
♪Love departs, hatred persists♪
♪الحب يرحل، والكراهية تبقى♪
♪I woke too soon to bygone bonds♪
♪استيقظت مبكرًا جدًا على الروابط القديمة♪
♪Forgetting the lost one in old dreams♪
♪نسيان المفقود في الأحلام القديمة♪
♪No longer waiting for estranged souls♪
♪لم يعد هناك انتظار للأرواح المنفصلة♪
♪Memories flow in the deep night♪
♪تتدفق الذكريات في الليل العميق♪
♪Illuminating lonely spirits♪
♪إضاءة الأرواح الوحيدة♪
♪Become an ordinary mortal♪
♪أصبح إنسانًا عاديًا♪
♪Next spring will open heart's doors♪
♪الربيع القادم سيفتح أبواب القلب♪
♪Not seeking a specific beloved♪
♪لا أبحث عن حبيب محدد♪
♪Gracefully embracing affections♪
♪احتضان المشاعر برشاقة♪